Elsie Clews Parsons Papers 1835-1944 Mss.Ms.Coll.29
American Philosophical Society
- Elsie Clews Parsons Papers II, 1898-1937
  - Series I. Professional Correspondence, 1898-1937
    - Harper's Weekly, 1913-16 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Metz, Charles A. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Harris, Annie Erna, 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hart, Walter Morris, 1919; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hasboune, [J.?], 1912-14 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hayshaw, Beatrice M. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See Ser.IV. Nova Scotia - Notebook #1, 1923
    - Heretics Club, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Herrera, Tanita, 1922-23 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Herskovits, Frances, 1929-31 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See also Ser.I, Herskovits, Melville - Mss. - Suriname Folk-Lore
    - Herskovits, Melville J., 1927-1941; 3 items (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Herskovits, Melville J. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #1, 1929-31 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #2, 1932-36 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Herskovits, Melville J. - Mss. - Suriname Folk-Lore, [ca. 1936] (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Herskovits, Frances (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Herzog, George, 1927; ALS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hibbert Journal, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hill, Mary A., 1907 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hill, W. W., 1940-1941; 2 items (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hilles, Charles D., 1912 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See Ser.IV, American Ethnology SW - Notebook
    - Hispanic Society of America, 1917; 1924 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hitchcock, Frederick H., 1910 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hodge, F.W., 1929 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Cushing, Frank Hamilton - Mss. - "Oraibe Creation Myth" (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
        -See Ser.III, Mss. - "Spanish Elements in the Kachina Cult of the Pueblos" - Corr.
    - Hollingworth, Greta S., 1921 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Holmes, W.H., 1912 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Holt, Hamilton (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See Ser.I, The Independent
    - Henry Holt & Co. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See Ser.III, Mss. - Laws of Imitation - Correspondence
    - House, Grace Bigelow, 1919 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Howells, John Mead, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Huebsch, B.W., 1920 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hughes, Lawrence (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #1, 1914 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #2, 1915-17 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Lawrence Hughes family, 1915-22 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hughes, Myra Hamilton, 1913?; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Hyllested, Mlle., 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - The Independent, 1906-13 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Holt, Hamilton (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
        -See also Ser.III, Mss. - "Nursery Bug-A-Boos"
    - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1933 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - The International Journal of Ethics, 1915-17 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      - Tufts, James H. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Jelliffe, Smith Ely, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Johnson, Alvin S., 1928; ALS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Johnson, Alvin S., 1918?-35; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See also Ser.I, Gillett, Frederick
      -See also Ser.I, The New Republic
    - Johnson, Eleanor H., n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Johnson, Grace Nail, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Johnson, Melville - Mss. - "Taos the Brilliant", n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Johnstone, Arthur Edward, 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Journal of Abnormal Psychology, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Journal of Philosophy, Psychology and Scientific Method, 1912-17 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Just, E.E., 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Kelley, Florence, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Kennaday, Paul, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Kennard, Edward A., 1934-36 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Kerr, Archibald, 1912 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Keur, Dorothy L., 1940; ALS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Kidder, Alfred V., 1926; TLS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Kidder, Alfred V., 1920-35 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See also Ser.I, Brew, J.O.
    - King, Epsie, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., 1936 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Knowles, Squire, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Krempin, L. C., 1909? (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
    - Kroeber, Alfred L. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 4)
      -See also Ser.I, Bourne, Randolph
      -See also Ser.IV, Zuni - Notebook, [Journal #1], 1915
      -See also Ser.IV, Zuni - Notebook, [Topics #2], 1915
      -See also Ser.IV, Zuni - Notebook, 1915-16
      -See also Ser.IV, Zuni - [Notes by Alfred L. Kroeber] #1-5, [ca.1919?]
      -See also Ser,VI, Kroeber, Alfred
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Kroeber, Alfred L.
      - Folder #1, 1915-17 (Box Paper-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #2, 1918 (Box Paper-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #3, 1919 (Box Paper-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #4, 1920-21 (Box Paper-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #5, 1922-34 (Box Paper-II Series-I: 4)
      - Folder #6, n.d. (Box Paper-II Series-I: 4)
    - Laboratory of Anthropology (Santa Fe, N.M.), 1931; 1935; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See also Ser.I, Nusbaum, Jesse
    - Laboratory of Anthropology (Santa Fe, N.M.) - Minutes, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - La Farge, C. Grant (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See also Ser.III, Mss. - "An Island Bewitched"
      - Folder #1, 1913 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Folder #2, 1914?-21; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - La Farge, C. Grant - Mss. - "Rivers and Recollections" (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - La Farge, C. Grant - Poems, 1918-21; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - LaFarge, Oliver, 1926; TLS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - La Farge, Oliver (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See Ser.III, Mss. - "Spanish Elements in the Kachina Cult of the Pueblos" - Correspondence
    - Laroche, Thimoléon, 1912 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Law, George, 1925; 1929-1936 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Lebosse, Dan, 1931 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Lesser, Alexander, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Lewis, Margaret, 1927; 2 items (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Lewis, Margaret (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See also Ser.IV, Zuni - Notebook, 1915-17
      -See also Ser.IV, Zuni - Notes, 1932
      - Folder #1, 1916?-33 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Lichtenberger, J.P. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See Ser.I, Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science
    - Lindeman, E.C., 1929 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Linton, Adeline, 1940; TLS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Lippman, Walter, 1916; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - The Literary Agency of London, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Loeb, Edwin M., 1932 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Lowie, Robert H. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See also Ser.VI, Lowie, Robert
    - Luhan, Mabel Dodge, 1927; ALS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Luhan, Mabel Dodge (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See also Ser.IV, Taos - Notes, [ca.1930]
      -See also Ser.VI, Luhan, Mabel Dodge
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Luhan, Mabel Dodge
      - Folder #1, [1922]; 1925; 1928; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - McCutcheon, John T., 1932; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - McGraw, Clara Louise (Mrs. Donald), n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - McGuire, Mary C., 1905 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - McLennan, Grace, 1921 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Mack, Julian W., 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Marlborough, Consuelo (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See Ser.I, Spurgeon, Caroline
    - Marn, John, 1913? (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Martin, Paul S., 1933 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Martin, Walton, 1906; 1932; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Martinez, Lorenzo, 1929; 1936 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Massachusetts Woman Suffrage Association, 1908 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - The Masses, 1915-19; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Dell, Floyd (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Eastman, Crystal (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Eastman, Max (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Mayer, Julius M., 1906 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - The Mayor's Independence Day Committee, 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Medical Review of Reviews, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Mencken, H.L., 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Merz, Charles, 1920? (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Metz, Charles A. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See Ser.I, Harper's Weekly
    - Miller, Alice Duer, 1919?; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See also Ser.III, Mss. - "Shall We Send Our Daughters to College"
    - Miller, H.W., 1906-12; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Mills, Ogden L., 1922 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Milne, F.W. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Moffat, Yard & Company, 1911 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Moody, M., 1906 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Moore, J.B., 1913 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Moorehead, [Warren K.], [1922] (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Montague, W.P., n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Morgan, C. Stuart, 1923 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Morris, Newbold, 1936 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Morris, Stephen (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      -See Ser.IV, Nova Scotia - Notes, [1923]
    - Morse, Edward S., 1920 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Museum of Northern Arizona, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Museum of the American Indian, 1918 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Nadal[?], F.W., n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Naismith, Grace, 1934 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1920 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Johnson, James Weldon (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - National Committee on Federal Legislation for Birth Control, Inc., 1934 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - National Hughes Alliance. Women's Committee, 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - The New International Encyclopedia, 1914 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Colby, F.M. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - The New International Year Book, 1914 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Colby, F.M. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - "The New Passion-alism", [1911?] (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - The New Republic, 1915-20?; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Croly, Herbert (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Johnson, Alvin S. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Littell, Philip (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Littell, R. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
        -See also Ser.I, Hackett, Francis
    - New Review, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - New School for Social Research, 1919 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - New York (City). Office of the President of the Borough of Manhattan, 1908 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - New York Academy of Sciences, 1917-35 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - New York Times, 1914-17; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
      - Wiley, Louis (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
        -See also Ser.X, Corr. - New York Times
    - New York Tribune, 1915-16 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - The New Yorker (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Nock, Albert Jay, 1921 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - Nusbaum, Jesse L., 1931-35 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 5)
    - O'Brien, Katherine M., 1936 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - O'Donovan, Gerald, 1909 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Open Court Publishing Company, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Opler, Morris Edward, 1939-1941; 2 items (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Opler, Morris E. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      -See also Ser.VI, Opler, Morris
      - Folder #1, 1931-32 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      - Folder #2, 1933-34 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      - Folder #3, 1935-36; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Opler, Morris E. - Mss. - "An Analysis of Mesclavo and Chiricahua Apache Social Organization, 1932 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Opler, Morris E. - Notes, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Pan American Union, 1913 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Pardo de Tavera, T.H., 1905 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Parsons, Elsie Clews. Fragment of "Bahama article" mss., n.d.; TMs (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Parsons, Geoffrey, 1922 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Parsons, Mary, n.d.; ALS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Peabody, Charles, 1920; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Peabody, George Foster, 1926; 2 TLsS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - People's Council of America, 1917; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      - Lochner, Louis P. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Percy, E., 1913-14? (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Peters, Andrew J., 1907?-36 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Peters, Martha R. Phillips, 1910-35; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Philadelphia Conference on Parenthood, 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Piedra Lumbre Cattle Company Ghost Ranch, 1934 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Pinchot, Gifford, 1905-08 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Plaza, M. Avelina de, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Popular Science Monthly, 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - PospC-sil, Francis, 1931; 1933 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Poyntz, Juliet Stuart, 1914 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Price, B.S., 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Pronger, Dorothy M., 1926 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      -See Ser.IV, Egyptian, Sudanese, and Arabian Tales - Notes, 1926
    - Psychoanalytic Review, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - The Psychological Review, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - The Public, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Public Education Association, 1914 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph, 1907 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Putnam, Emily James, 1906-19; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Putnam, Herbert, 1905?; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1907-19 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Race, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Radin, Paul, 1930 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Raup, Ida, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Ravage, M.E., 1918-19 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Ravenel, W. de C., 1919 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      plant specimen
    - Realso, Cleveland H., 1919 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Redfield, Robert, 1939; TLS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Redfield, Robert, 1929-35 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      -See also Ser.III, Mss. - Mitla: Town of the Souls
      -See also Ser.VI, Redfield, Robert
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Redfield, Robert
    - Redfield, [Robert] - Mss. - "The Coati and the Ceiba", [1935?] (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Reichard, Gladys A., 1927-1941; 7 items (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Reichard, Gladys A. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      -See also Ser.VI, Reichard, Gladys A.
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Reichard, Gladys
      - Folder #1, 1923-31 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      - Folder #2, 1932-36; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Reuter, E.B., 1930 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Reynolds, Paul R., 1906 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Rhodes, Harrison, 1913 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - 1932 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      -See Ser.IV, Mexico - Notes, 1930-32 [La Conquista, Santa Ana del Valle]
    - Roberts, Helen H., 1919-36 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Robinson, Evangeline M. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      -See Ser.IV, Nova Scotia - Notebook #9, 1923
    - Robinson, James Harvey, 1914; 1920; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Rodman, Henrietta, 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1906-09 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Root, Elihu, 1909 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Rosenbloom, Samuel, 1918 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Ross, E.A., 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Royal Anthropological Institute, 1918; 1920 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Russell, William F., 1939; 3 items (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Rydberg, P.A., 1919 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Sanger, Margaret, 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      - Sanger, William (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Sanger, William, 1916-17 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      -See also Ser.I, Sanger, Margaret
    - Sapir, Edward, 1918-36 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
      - Beaglehole, Ernest (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Santiago, Eligio, 1932 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Sargent, Mary T., 1920 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 6)
    - Schapiro, J. Salwyn, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - School and Society, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      - Cattell, James McKeen (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - The School of Philanthropy, 1906 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Schroeder, Theodore, 1906; 1914 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Scidmore, Eliza R., 1908? (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Scientific Monthly, 1916-36; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      - Cattell, James McKeen (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Scofield, S.W., 1914; 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Seager, Henry N. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See Ser.III, Mss. - "Property and Habit"
    - Sedgwick, Mary K., 1922 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Seligman, Edwin R.A., 1907 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Sedgwick, Shan, 1939; 3 items (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Selmer, Carl, 1930 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Service Espagnol d'Information, 1936 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - The Seven Arts, 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Shank, Burgess, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Shaw, Marion K., 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Silva, Adela, 1905-16 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Simkhovitch, Mary K., 1899-1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See also Ser.I, Greenwich House
    - Skinner, Alanson B., 1917 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Small, Albion W., 1913-16 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Smith, T.R. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See Ser.III, Mss. - "In the Southwest", Folders #1, #6, #10
    - Smythe, B.M., n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Snyder, Homer P., 1923 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Society of Friends of Mexico, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Sociological Review, 1915 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Sonneborn, H.B., Sr., 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Southwest Museum, 1935-36 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Southwest Society, 1919-23 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      ledger
    - Southwest Society - Membership Card file, 1919-22 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      - Day, Clarence (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
        -See Oversized
    - Spier, Ann Gayton, 1935-36 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Spier, Leslie (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See also Ser.III, Mss. - "Christian Rites in Zuni Ceremonialism" - Corr.
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - White, Leslie A.
      - Folder #1, 1918; 1920-1934 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      - Folder #2, 1935-37 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Spinden, Herbert J., 1922 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See also Ser.VII, Bursum Bill
    - Spurgeon, Caroline, 1918 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      - Marlborough, Consuelo (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Starr, Frederick, 1922 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Stimson, Henry L., 1906; 1920 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Stirling, Matthew W., 1940-1941; 3 TLsS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Stirling, Matthew W., 1930-37 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1915; 1936 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Stokes, Anson Phelps
    - Stokes, Helen Phelps, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Strong, Duncan, 1937; TLS (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Strong, Duncan, 1935; 1937 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - The Suffragist, 1920 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Sunday World, 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      - Wood, Charles W. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Sunwise Turn Bookshop, 1929 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - The Survey, 1916 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Swanton, John R., 1919; 1922 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See also Ser.III, Mss. - "Escape Up the Tree"
    - Swift, Charles N., 1906 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1906-27 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See also Ser.VI, Taft, William
    - Tanenbaum, Florence L., 1919? (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Teachers' Defense Committee, 1918 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Teall, Dorothy, 1932 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Teresa, L.M. Imilia, 1912 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Terrell, Clemmie S. - Mss. "Spirituals in Alabama", 1930 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See Ser.III, Mss. - "Spirituals in Alabama"
    - Thomas, William I. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See Ser.III, Mss. - "Two Methods of Ethnological Hypothesis"
    - Thompson, Martha, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Thown, Miss [?], 1905 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Thurnwald, Richard C., 1933 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Titiev, Morris (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      -See also Ser.VI, Titiev, Mischa
      - Folder #1, 1933-34 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      - Folder #2, 1935-37; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Toksvig, Signe K., 1920-29; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
      Signe Toksvig is Mrs. Francis Hackett
    - Toor, Frances, 1929-34; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Torrence, R., 1917-20 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 7)
    - Trager, George L., 1937 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - True, Clara D. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      - Edwards, A.M. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      - Law, George (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
        -See also Ser.II, Parsons, Herbert, 1920
      - Folder #1, 1910-13 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      - Folder #2, 1914-19 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      - Folder #3, 1920-22; 1934; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Tufts, James H. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See Ser.I, International Journal of Ethics
    - Tutting[?], R. Fulton, 1906 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Tutuiler, Julia R., 1911-13; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Underhill, Ruth (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - United States. Dept. of Justice, 1918 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - United States. Dept. of the Interior, 1912; n.d. (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See also Ser.IV, American Ethnology SW - Notebook
    - United States. Dept. of the Interior. Office of Indian Affairs, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - United States Civil Service Commission, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - University of California Press, 1935 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Univ. of California Press
    - University of Chicago, 1914-15 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Univ. of Chicago
    - Vaillant, George C., 1934 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Van Doren, Carl (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See Ser.I, Brearley School
    - Vassar College. Folk Lore Foundation (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Viking Press, Inc., 1934-35 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Viking Press, Inc.
    - Villarán, Benjamin, Jr., 1930 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See also Ser.IV, [Mexico] - Notes [taken by Benjamin Villarán, Jr.], 1930
    - Wallis, Wilson D., 1932-35 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
      -See also Ser.X, Corr. - Wallis, Wilson D.
    - Walton, Eda Lou, 1919 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Warrinder [?], Eleanor, 1906 (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)
    - Way, George P., [1925] (Box Papers-II Series-I: 8)